export default [
    {
        question: "brothers",
        answer: "frère"
    },
    {
        question: "sisters",
        answer: "sœur"
    },
    {
        question: "in law (m) တွေဆိုရှေ့မှာဘာထည့်ပေးရလဲ? step-father",
        answer: "beau"
    },
    {
        question: "in law (f) တွေဆိုရှေ့မှာဘာထည့်ပေးရလဲ? step-mom, sisten in law",
        answer: "belle"
    },
    {
        question: "step parents",
        answer: "beaux parents"
    },
    {
        question: "grandmother",
        answer: "la grand-mère",
        highlight: "I talks",
    },
    {
        question: "husband",
        answer: "le mari",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "wife",
        answer: "la femme",
        highlight: "She talks",
    },
    {
        question: "daughter",
        answer: "la fille",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "son",
        answer: "le fils",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "father",
        answer: "le père",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "mother",
        answer: "la mère",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "grandson",
        answer: "le petit-fils",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "granddaughter",
        answer: "la petite-fille",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "cousin (m)",
        answer: "le cousin",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "cousin (f)",
        answer: "la cousine",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "niece",
        answer: "la nièce",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "nephew",
        answer: "le neveu",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "uncle",
        answer: "l'oncle",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "aunt",
        answer: "la tante",
        highlight: "You talks",
    }
]